The Amanda Steele Show.
Tennessee House Republicans pass legislation allowing trained teachers to carry concealed handguns despite opposition from Democrat students and gun reform advocates.
Armed teachers, after undergoing training, can carry handguns without informing parents.
Wow.
Approval from school administrators and law enforcement is required for staff members to carry concealed handguns.
Now you explain to me how that is okay.
They're also not paying these teachers enough.
They're not giving them enough resources.
So their mental health for, I mean, I've seen so many teachers say that they are burnt out, you know, that they are just frustrated.
And so just like that, you create a whole situation that goes to a whole other level.
So this also concerns me because we already see that the police are being militarized and now they're militarizing the teachers.
So it's also just like, so y'all aren't giving teachers the resources that they need to teach, but you're finding money to get, because they're gonna, I'm telling you, they're going to give them guns.
You think they're going to give them guns?
I, everything is about money in this country.
And I believe that what's going to happen is that there's going to get a contract to where they, the school board arms the teachers, but they might buy the weapons from Israel.
Wow.
When you think about like how money flows and the reason why certain laws pass in this country, a lot of times when it don't make sense, it's because it makes money.
That sounds worse than the school Mr. Clark was at.
Mr. Clark, Mr. Clark, who's going to take care of the school if you ain't here, Mr. Clark?
Mr. Clark in there with a pistol.
We are, we are, we are.